Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Negotiations
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1960-1963, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1973-1976, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC) for 1982-1985, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1952-1954, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1982-1985 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1982-1985, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Network Staff Announcers (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1985-1988 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1973-1976, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1979-1982 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Network Staff Announcers (CBS) for 1982-1985 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1960-1963 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1969-1972, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1973-1976, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Network Staff Announcers (NBC) for 1982-1985, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC) for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC) for 1969-1972, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC) for 1973-1976, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC) for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC) for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC) for 1982-1985 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC) for 1982-1985, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1956-1958, 1954-1957 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1958-1960 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1960-1963, 1960-1962 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1963-1966, 1963-1965 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1966-1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1966-1969, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1969-1972, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1973-1976, Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [and Announcers] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1973-1976, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1982-1985 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1982-1985, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [From Binder] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1985-1988 [1 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [From Binder] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1985-1988 [2 of 3], 1986 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Network Staff Newspersons [From Binder] (ABC, CBS, NBC) for 1985-1988 [3 of 3], 1986 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (CBS) for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (CBS) for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (CBS) for 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (CBS) for 1973-1976, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (CBS) for 1976-1979, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (CBS) for 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (NBC) for 1966-1969, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (NBC) for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (NBC) for 1973-1976, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (NBC) for 1976-1979, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Network Staff Newspersons (NBC) for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Non-Broadcast Industrial Code for 1978-1982, 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Non-Broadcast Industrial Code for 1982-1985 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Non-Broadcast Industrial Code for 1982-1985: from Binder (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Non-Broadcast Industrial Code for 1985-1988, 1985-1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Non-Broadcast Industrial Code for 1985-1988: from Binder, 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Non-Broadcast, Slide film, Cassettes, Commercials: Groot, Ken's Material, May 1974-May 1975 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Non-Broadcast, Slide film, Cassettes, Commercials: Groot, Ken's Material, Jun-Sep 1975 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Phono Code for 1951-1953, 1949-1952 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Phono Code for 1954-1955, 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Phono Code for 1957-1959 (Groot's Material) (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Phono Code for 1959-1962 (Groot's Material), Apr-Sep 1959 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Phono Code for 1959-1962 (Groot's Material), Oct 1959-Feb 1960 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Phono Code for 1962-1965 (Groot's Material) (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Phono Code for 1962-1965: Signatories, 1963-1964 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Phono Code for 1965-1968 (Groot's Material), 1964 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Phono Code for 1965-1968 (Groot's Material), 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971 (Groot's Material), 1967 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Phono Code for 1968-1971 (Groot's Material) (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974 (Groot's Material), Mar-May 1970 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974 (Groot's Material), Jun-Dec 1970 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974 (Groot's Material) (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Phono Code for 1971-1974, Proposals from Nashville Local, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977 (Groot's Material), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977 (Groot's Material), Jan-Jun 1974 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Phono Code for 1974-1977 (Groot's Material), Jul-Dec 1974 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980 (Groot's Material), 1975-1977 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Phono Code for 1977-1980 (Groot's Material), 1978 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Phono Code for 1980-1983 (Groot's Material), 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Phono Code for 1983-1986, 1983-1984 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Phono Code for 1986-1989 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - PRN (Physicians Radio Network), 1980 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Production Memorandum: Actors, Emcees, Singers, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Production Memorandum: Announcers, 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Production Memorandum: Announcers, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Production Memorandum: Newscasters, Jul-Aug 1957 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Production Memorandum: Newscasters, Sep 1957 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Production Memorandum: Newscasters, Oct 1957 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Production Memorandum: Newscasters, Dec 1957 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Production Memorandum: Sportscasters, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Proposals for all Codes and Contracts, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Proposals for all Codes and Contracts, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Proposals for all Codes and Contracts, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Proposals for all Codes and Contracts, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - RKO General: KMJ, KRTH, KMJ-TV, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - RKO General: Radio Network Staff Newspersons for 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - RKO General: WNJU-TV, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - [General Teleradio Inc.] RKO General: WOR, 1950-1951 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - [General Teleradio Inc.] RKO General: WOR [IBEW Strike and Related Materials], 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - [General Teleradio Inc.] RKO General: WOR, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - [General Teleradio Inc.] RKO General: WOR for 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - [General Teleradio Inc.] RKO General: WOR, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1956-1958 (Groot's Material) (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1956-1958 (Groot's Material), 1957 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1958-1961 (Groot's Material) (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1960-1964 (Groot's Material), 1959-1961 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1964-1967, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1964-1967, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1964-1967, Artist's Contracts, 1964-1966 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, Jan-Aug 1967 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, Sep 1967 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, Oct-Dec 1967 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, Management Bulletins (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - RKO General: WOR for 1967-1970, Union Bulletins (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM-FM-TV for 1970-1973, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM-FM-TV for 1970-1973, Jan-May 1970 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM-FM-TV for 1970-1973, Jun-Aug 1970 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM-FM-TV for 1970-1973, Sep-Dec 1970 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM-FM-TV for 1970-1973, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM-FM-TV for 1970-1973, Agreement, Mar 1972 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1973-1976, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1973-1976, Jan-Jul 1973 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1973-1976, Aug-Dec 1973 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1973-1976, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1973-1976, Agreement, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1973-1976, Related Arbitrations, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1977-1980, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1977-1980 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1977-1980, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1977-1980, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1977-1980, Agreement, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1980-1983, Jan-May 1980 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1980-1983, Jun-Aug 1980 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1980-1983, Sep-Dec 1980 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1980-1983, Agreement Draft and Signed, Mar 1981 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV for 1980-1983, Ballots and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-May 1981 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV Correspondence and Related Materials, Jul-Dec 1981 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982-1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV Correspondence re: Chris Cunningham, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - RKO General: WOR-AM, WXLO, WOR-TV Correspondence re: Sara Lee Kessler, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - [Commercial] Radio Broadcasting, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - [Commercial] Radio Broadcasting for 1963-1966, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - [Commercial] Radio Broadcasting for 1976-1979, 1976-1978 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - [Commercial] Radio Broadcasting for 1979-1982 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - [Commercial] Radio Broadcasting for 1982-1985 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1972-1975 (mostly waivers), 1973 (Box 64, Folder 12A)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1975-1978 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1979-1982, 1978-1981 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Radio Recorded Commercials for 1985-1988 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Rule 12-B, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Rule 12-B: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966-1972 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Rule 12-B: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Rule 12-B: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Rule 12-B: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977-1979 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Rule 12-B: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Shadow Network for 1979-1982 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Shadow Network for 1982-1985, 1982-1984 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Shadow Network for 1985-1988, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Signatories: Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Signatories: Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Slide Film for 1964-1966, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Slide Film for 1967-1969, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Slide Film for 1969-1972 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Slide Film for 1973-1976, 1973-1975 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Spanish International Network, 1978-1982 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - STARR KABL for 1972-1975, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Sterling [Information Services] Movies Inc. for 1963-1966 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1962-1963, Teleguide (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1963-1965: Teleguide (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1965-1967: Teleguide (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1967-1969: Teleguide (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1967-1969: Teleguide, 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1967-1970: Channels Six and Eight, 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1970-1972: Manhattan Cable Television (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1970-1972: Manhattan Cable Television, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1973 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1970-1973: Teleguide, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Sterling Information Services for 1970-1973: Teleguide, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Strike: CBS, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Strike: Commercials, Correspondence, 1975-1979, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Strike: General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Strike: General, Lists of Protestors, [1980s] (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Strike: IBEW, Agreement, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Strike: IBEW, Attendance Records, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Strike: IBEW, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Strike: IBEW, Mailing Lists, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Strike: IBEW, Photos, [1972] (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Strike: KFWB, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Strike: KYW, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Strike: NABET, Attendance Logs, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Strike: NABET, Ballots, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Strike: NABET, Correspondence, 1964-1986 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Strike: Television Prime Time, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Strike: WAG, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Strike: WBZ, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Strike: WHLI, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Strike: WIND, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Strike: WINS, Agreement, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Strike: WINS, Agreement, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Strike: WINS, Agreement, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Strike: WINS, Agreement, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Strike: WINS, Agreement, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Strike: WINS, Agreement, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Strike: WINS, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Strike: WINS, Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Strike: WINS, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Strike: WINS, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Strike: WINS, Picketing and Mailing Lists, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Strike: WINS, Picketing Assignments, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Strike: WINS, Press, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Strike: WINS, Sponsors List, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Strike: WNJR, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Strike: WNJR, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Strike: WOR, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Strike: WTFM Disciplinary Proceedings (includes photographs), 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Strike: WTFM, includes photographs, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Television: Basic Cable, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Television: Basic Cable, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Television: Basic Cable, 1982-1983 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "4 Play", 1983 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "Beacon Hill" Series, 1975-1977 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Bravo, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "Charley's Aunt", 1982 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Closed Circuit TV, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1960-1964 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials (including video cassette negotiations), 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Jun 1982 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, Jul-Dec 1982 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Home Box Office (HBO), 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO Correspondence, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO Correspondence, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO Correspondence, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO Correspondence, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO Correspondence, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO, "Freddie Prinze and Friends", 1976 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO, "Hindenburg", 1980 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO, Pension and Welfare Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, HBO, "Pretzels", 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, International Telemeter, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Kenyon Festival Theatre, 1981-1982 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Live Pick-up Shows, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Muzak, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Negotiations, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Pension and Health Reports, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "Piaf", 1981 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Proposals on Use of Commercials, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, Sterling Manhattan and Teleprompter Cable TV, 1970-1972 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "Union Strategies for Cable TV", 1974 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "What Does It Mean to You?", Oct 1957 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "Woman of the Year" Documentary, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Television: Cable TV/Pay TV, "The Year in TV" TV Guide Special, 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Television: National Code for 1960-1963 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Television: National Code for 1960-1963, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Television: National Code for 1963-1966, 1963-1964 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Television: National Code for 1969-1972 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Television: National Code for 1973-1976, 1973-1977 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Television: National Code for 1976-1979, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Television: National Code for 1979-1982, Jan-Sep 1979 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Television: National Code for 1979-1982, Oct-Dec 1979 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Television: National Code for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Television: National Code for 1979-1982, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Television: National Code for 1979-1982 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Television: National Code for 1982-1985 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Television: National Code for 1985-1988 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Television: NY Local Code for 1963-1966, 1963-1964 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Television: NY Local Code for 1972-1975 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Television: NY Local Code for 1973-1976 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Television: NY Local Code for 1976-1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Television: NY Local Code for 1979-1982, 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Television: NY Local Code for 1985-1988 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Television: Primetime AFTRA-SAG Notes, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Television: Primetime [From Binder] Correspondence, Notes and Related Materials, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Television: Primetime [From Binder], Meeting Minutes, Jun 11-24, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Television: Primetime [From Binder], Meeting Minutes, Jun 25-29, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Television: Primetime, Negotiations Summary, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Television: Primetime [from Binder], Producers Proposals to AFTRA, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Television: Primetime [from Binder], Producers Proposals to SAG, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Television: Primetime [from Binder], Proposals Index Part I, Salaries and Schedules, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Television: Primetime [from Binder], Proposals Index Part II, General Provisions, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Television: Primetime [from Binder], Proposals Index Part III-VII, Minors, Singers, Dancers, Stunt Performers, Pay-TV or Videos, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Television: Primetime [from Binder], Proposals Index Part VIII and IX, SAG/AFTRA, Parity, Clarification, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Television: Production Memoranda, Various Titles and Companies, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Television: Public Television for 1979-1983 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Television: Public Television for 1983-1986 (Box 68, Folder 20)